Register of the Raymond Moley papers, 1902-1971
Hoover Institution Archives
- GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1912-1969 (Boxes 2-62)
  - Laski, J. Harold, 1933 (Folder 44)
  - Lasky, Victor, 1954-1960 (Folder 45)
  - Last, Theodore, 1934 (Folder 46)
  - Latimer, J. A., 1934 (Folder 47)
  - Latone, Stanley J., 1965 (Folder 48)
  - Laufer, Emma, 1920 (Folder 49)
  - Laurie, M. J., 1938 (Folder 50)
  - Lauryssen, Gaston, 1938 (Folder 51)
  - Lausche, Frank J., 1948 (Folder 52)
  - Lavers, C. W., 1934 (Folder 53)
  - Lawson, Clarence Allen, 1932 (Folder 54)
  - Lawson, William U., 1943 (Folder 55)
  - Lawton, Edward M., Jr., 1963 (Folder 56)
  - Lauritzen, H. D., 1958 (Folder 57)
  - Lawes, Lewis E., 1930 (Folder 58)
  - Lay, Arthur J., 1936 (Folder 59)
  - Laycock, J. N., 1934 (Folder 60)
  - Leach, Henry Goddard, 1931 (Folder 61)
  - Leachman, Charles, 1942 (Folder 62)
  - League, T. J., 1928-1934 (Folder 63)
  - Leahy, J. Gordon, 1932 (Folder 64)
  - Lear, Ben, 1951 (Folder 65)
  - Lear, John, 1939 (Folder 66)
  - Leary, H. F., 1946 (Folder 67)
  - LeBoutillier, Cornelia, 1952-1964 (Folder 68)
  - Lechner, Robert Louis, 1963 (Folder 69)
  - LeCron, J. D., 1934 (Folder 70)
  - Ledbetter, Eleanor E., 1919 (Folder 71)
  - LeDuke, Frank A., 1933 (Folder 72)
  - LeDuke, J. A., 1934 (Folder 73)
  - Lee, Algernon, 1931 (Folder 74)
  - Lee, Hubert F., 1934 (Folder 75)
  - Lee, Ivy, 1934 (Folder 76)
  - Lee, J. Bracken, 1951 (Folder 77)
  - Lee, Luke, 1933 (Folder 78)
  - Lee, Stanley, 1934 (Folder 79)
  - Lee, W. L., 1963 (Folder 80)
  - Leedle, Arthur C., 1942 (Folder 81)
  - Leffingwell, Russell, 1934-1936 (Folder 82)
  - Lefkowitz, Henry, 1924 (Folder 83)
  - Leggett, John, 1951 (Folder 84)
  - LeHand, D. J., 1932-1933 (Folder 85)
  - LeHand, Marguerite (Missy), 1934-1938 (Folder 86)
  - Lehman, Herbert M., 1930-1937 (Folder 87)
  - Lehman, Leo, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Leigh, Robert D., 1932 (Folder 2)
  - Leiser, Clara, 1931 (Folder 3)
  - Leiserson, William M., 1924 (Folder 4)
  - Lelyveld, Arthur J., 1933 (Folder 5)
  - Lemke, Ross D., 1939 (Folder 6)
  - Lenk, George L., 1933 (Folder 7)
  - Lenkey, John, III, 1965 (Folder 8)
  - Lennox, John S., 1935 (Folder 9)
  - Lenney, John J., 1952 (Folder 10)
  - Leon, Maurice, 1932 (Folder 11)
  - Leon, Rene, 1932 (Folder 12)
  - Leonard, J. Paul, 1938 (Folder 13)
  - Leonard, Oscar, 1934 (Folder 14)
  - Leonard, W. B., 1933 (Folder 15)
  - Leonard, William D., 1933-1934 (Folder 16)
  - Leonard, William F., 1965 (Folder 17)
  - Lerner, Max, 1950-1951 (Folder 18)
  - Lescohier, D. D., 1920 (Folder 19)
  - Lesher, Lou Denison, 1933 (Folder 20)
  - Lesher, Robert, 1916 (Folder 21)
  - Leslie, John W., 1965 (Folder 22)
  - Lester, Richard A., 1934 (Folder 23)
  - LeSoeur, Arthur, 1934 (Folder 24)
  - Levant, Oscar, 1939 (Folder 25)
  - Levene, A. H., 1932 (Folder 26)
  - Levine, Isaac Don, 1933-1934 (Folder 27)
  - Levine, Leon, 1938 (Folder 28)
  - Levine, Manuel, 1928-1932 (Folder 29)
  - Levis, William E., 1936-1937 (Folder 30)
  - Levitt, Albert, 1929 (Folder 31)
  - Levy, Felix H., 1936 (Folder 32)
  - Levy, Newman, 1933 (Folder 33)
  - Lewald, Leon, 1924 (Folder 34)
  - Lewerth, Catherine, 1938 (Folder 35)
  - Lewin, Charles, 1957-1958 (Folder 36)
  - Lewin, William, 1946 (Folder 37)
  - Lewis, Anthony, 1958 (Folder 38)
  - Lewis, Burdett G., 1943 (Folder 39)
  - Lewis, David J., 1932 (Folder 40)
  - Lewis, Frederic V., 1929-1933 (Folder 41)
  - Lewis, Fulton, Jr., 1940-1942 (Folder 42)
  - Lewis, Jerry, 1939 (Folder 43)
  - Lewis, Ludwig C., 1942 (Folder 44)
  - Lewis, Montgomery H., 1934 (Folder 45)
  - Lewis, Read, 1928 (Folder 46)
  - Lewis, Robert C., 1946 (Folder 47)
  - Lewis, Robert E., 1932 (Folder 48)
  - Lewis, Robert M., 1946 (Folder 49)
  - Lewis, William Draper, 1927-1933 (Folder 50)
  - Lewisohn, Adolph, 1928 (Folder 51)
  - Lewis, Willmott, 1934 (Folder 52)
  - Lewisohn, Margaret, 1937-1938 (Folder 53)
  - Lewisohn, Samuel A., 1938-1939 (Folder 54)
  - Lichenstein, Charles M., 1965 (Folder 55)
  - Lichliter, M. H., 1955 (Folder 56)
  - Licht, Emanuel H., 1938 (Folder 57)
  - Lidz, Theodore, 1965 (Folder 58)
  - Liebowitz, I. J., 1932 (Folder 59)
  - Light, Evelyn, 1934 (Folder 60)
  - Ligon, Wister H., 1963 (Folder 61)
  - Lincoln, Edmond E., 1943-1954 (Folder 62)
  - Lincoln, John C., 1952 (Folder 63)
  - Lincoln, John G., 1964 (Folder 64)
  - Linder, Clarence R., 1943 (Folder 65)
  - Lindley, Ernest K., 1934-1966 (Folder 66)
  - Lindley, F. U., 1936 (Folder 67)
  - Lindsay, John V., 1959 (Folder 68)
  - Lindsay, Samuel McCume, 1919-1932 (Folder 69)
  - Lindsay, Thomas, 1932 (Folder 70)
  - Lindseth, Elmer L., 1959 (Folder 71)
  - Linn, Elizabeth, 1928 (Folder 72)
  - Lipman, Walter, 1948-1960 (Folder 73)
  - Lipscomb, Glenard P., 1954-1955 (Folder 74)
  - Lipson, Isaac B., 1915 (Folder 75)
  - Lissitzyn, J. J., 1934 (Folder 76)
  - List, Murray D., 1955 (Folder 77)
  - Lister, William, n.d. (Folder 78)
  - Litchfield, P. W., 1938 (Folder 79)
  - Little, E. J., 1936 (Folder 80)
  - Livermore, Henrietta W., 1931 (Folder 81)
  - Livingston, Edwin A., 1931 (Folder 82)
  - Livingston, Goodhue, 1962 (Folder 83)
  - Llewellyn, Karl N., 1930-1934 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Lloyd, John H., 1934 (Folder 2)
  - Lockwood, Paul E., 1946 (Folder 3)
  - Lodge, John Davis, 1951 (Folder 4)
  - Lodge, Rupert C., 1944 (Folder 5)
  - Loeb, William, 1952-1958 (Folder 6)
  - Loesch, Frank J., 1928-1930 (Folder 7)
  - Lofton, H. M., 1932 (Folder 8)
  - Logan, Albert J., 1941 (Folder 9)
  - Logan, M. M., 1937 (Folder 10)
  - Lohman, H. W., 1932 (Folder 11)
  - Lonergan, Augustine, 1934-1937 (Folder 12)
  - Lomax, Lowell, 1933 (Folder 13)
  - Long, Breckinridge, 1935-1936 (Folder 14)
  - Long, John C., 1941-1942 (Folder 15)
  - Longstreet, Helen D., 1937 (Folder 16)
  - Loomis, Frank D., 1920 (Folder 17)
  - Loomis, John A., 1965 (Folder 18)
  - Lorenz, Keith, 1954 (Folder 19)
  - Lorenzen, A. F., 1932 (Folder 20)
  - Lother, Edward M., 1951 (Folder 21)
  - Loudagin, N. F., 1942-1943 (Folder 22)
  - Love, Donald M., 1933 (Folder 23)
  - Love, John W., 1932-1956. See also SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, Box 222
    - 1932-1935 (Folder 24)
    - 1936 (Folder 25)
    - 1937 (Folder 26)
    - 1938 (Folder 27)
    - 1939 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - 1940 (Folder 2)
    - 1941 (Folder 3)
    - 1942 (Folder 4)
    - 1943 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - General (Folder 2)
  - Love, Margaret, 1962 (Folder 3)
  - Love, T. B., 1934 (Folder 4)
  - Love, William F., 1931 (Folder 5)
  - Love, William T., 1934 (Folder 6)
  - Lovejoy, C. E., 1933 (Folder 7)
  - Lovejoy, F. W., 1938 (Folder 8)
  - Loveman, Amy, 1934 (Folder 9)
  - Lovesy, W. H., 1929 (Folder 10)
  - Lorett, Lew, 1936 (Folder 11)
  - Lovett, Robert A., 1934-1951 (Folder 12)
  - Lovett, Samuel Murray, 1930 (Folder 13)
  - Lowden, Frank O., 1940 (Folder 14)
  - Lowenthal, Max, 1950 (Folder 15)
  - Lowry, Edward G., 1936 (Folder 16)
  - Lowry, Frank C., 1939 (Folder 17)
  - Lubin, Simon J., 1932-1934 (Folder 18)
  - Luce, Charles F., 1949 (Folder 19)
  - Luchars, Robert B., 1942 (Folder 20)
  - Ludington, Katharine, 1927-1929 (Folder 21)
  - Lull, H. M., 1937 (Folder 22)
  - Lum, Merritt, 1965 (Folder 23)
  - Lumsdem, Mary, 1932 (Folder 24)
  - Lundell, William, 1933 (Folder 25)
  - Lupton, James J., 1934 (Folder 26)
  - Lyden, Leo V., 1959 (Folder 27)
  - Lynch, Thomas R., 1947-1951 (Folder 28)
  - Lynd, Robert S., 1931 (Folder 29)
  - Lynn, George W., 1936 (Folder 30)
  - Lyons, Charlton Havard, 1962-1965 (Folder 31)
  - Lyons, Eugene, 1943-1964 (Folder 32)
  - Lyons, Frank P., 1939 (Folder 33)
  - Lyons, Grant, 1941 (Folder 34)
  - Lyons, James J., 1931 (Folder 35)
  - Lyons, Leonard, 1938 (Folder 36)
  - Maass, John, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - MaCauley, Alvan, 1939 (Folder 2)
  - Macdonald, Dwight, 1933 (Folder 3)
  - Machanan, A. W., 1928-1940 (Folder 4)
  - Maclachlan, Mrs. J. M., 1934 (Folder 5)
  - Macmillan Company, 1926-1927 (Folder 6)
  - Macomber, Mabel E., 1930 (Folder 7)
  - Macomber, W. B., 1960 (Folder 8)
  - Macrae, John, 1929 (Folder 9)
  - Madden, James, 1939 (Folder 10)
  - Maffit, Mam E., 1924 (Folder 11)
  - Magill, Kathy, 1964 (Folder 12)
  - Magor, John, 1935 (Folder 13)
  - Magnusson, Leiter, 1933 (Folder 14)
  - Magnusson, Warren G., 1956 (Folder 15)
  - Magorn, E. A., 1939 (Folder 16)
  - Mahan, Edna, 1933 (Folder 17)
  - Mahler, Robert F., 1963 (Folder 18)
  - Mahone, George A., 1922 (Folder 19)
  - Mahoney, D. G., 1937 (Folder 20)
  - Mahoney, Jim, 1934 (Folder 21)
  - Mahoney, John J., 1923-1932 (Folder 22)
  - Mahoney, Joseph E., 1948 (Folder 23)
  - Mahoney, Walter J., 1958-1966 (Folder 24)
  - Maier, William J., 1922 (Folder 25)
  - Mair, J., 1928 (Folder 26)
  - Malkind, Samuel L., 1933 (Folder 27)
  - Mallon, Jennifer, n.d. (Folder 28)
  - Mallon, Paul, 1933-1934 (Folder 29)
  - Malmed, A. T., 1933 (Folder 30)
  - Malone, Dudley Field, 1938 (Folder 31)
  - Malone, Dumas, 1932-1938 (Folder 32)
  - Maloney, J. E., 1918 (Folder 33)
  - Maloney, John F., 1937 (Folder 34)
  - Maloney, Ronald A., 1963 (Folder 35)
  - Mandel, Arch, 1924 (Folder 36)
  - Manders, John E., 1952 (Folder 37)
  - Manion, Clarence, 1951 (Folder 38)
  - Manley, Harris S., 1954 (Folder 39)
  - Mann, J. L., 1959 (Folder 40)
  - Manning, Dorothy S., 1933 (Folder 41)
  - Manning, E. W., 1939 (Folder 42)
  - Manning, John, n.d. (Folder 43)
  - Manning, William T., 1934 (Folder 44)
  - Manoha, 1953-1954 (Folder 45)
  - Manuel, Ralph, 1938 (Folder 46)
  - Maphis, Charles G., 1929-1931 (Folder 47)
  - Marcial-Dorado, Carolina, 1933 (Folder 48)
  - Marcus, J. A., 1934 (Folder 49)
  - Margold, Stella K., 1934 (Folder 50)
  - Markel, Lester, 1931-1933 (Folder 51)
  - Marmaduke, H. C., 1942 (Folder 52)
  - Marriam, Charles E., 1925 (Folder 53)
  - Marsh, Beatrice H., 1925 (Folder 54)
  - Marsh, E. G., 1934 (Folder 55)
  - Marsh, Gladys, 1963 (Folder 56)
  - Marsh, Harry W., 1932 (Folder 57)
  - Marshall, Carrington T., 1932 (Folder 58)
  - Marshall, Clarence G., 1947 (Folder 59)
  - Marshall, George P., 1935-1954 (Folder 60)
  - Marshall, John, 1931 (Folder 61)
  - Marshall, L. C., 1929-1933 (Folder 62)
  - Marshall, Verne, 1940 (Folder 63)
  - Marshutz, James W. B., 1947 (Folder 64)
  - Martin, C. D., 1954 (Folder 65)
  - Martin, I. Jack, 1953 (Folder 66)
  - Martin, Joseph W., 1942-1946 (Folder 67)
  - Martin, Kenneth, 1931 (Folder 68)
  - Martin, Paul, 1955-1959 (Folder 69)
  - Martin, T. J., 1953 (Folder 70)
  - Marting, Albert L., 1943-1956 (Folder 71)
  - Marting, J. C., 1932-1940 (Folder 72)
  - Marx, Groucho, 1953 (Folder 73)
  - Marx, Robert S., 1932 (Folder 74)
  - Marx, Rudolph, 1964 (Folder 75)
  - Maschke, Maurice, 1924 (Folder 76)
  - Mason, Alfred B., 1960 (Folder 77)
  - Mason, Clarence I., 1931 (Folder 78)
  - Mason, E. D., 1963 (Folder 79)
  - Mason, Frank E., 1964 (Folder 80)
  - Mason, J. Rupert, 1932 (Folder 81)
  - Masotti, Louis H., 1967 (Folder 82)
  - Massey, Vincent, 1933-1934 (Folder 83)
  - Masters, Edgar Lee, 1934 (Folder 84)
  - Maston, P. B., n.d. (Folder 85)
  - Mateer, R. L., 1952 (Folder 86)
  - Mathews, William R., 1941 (Folder 87)
  - Matson, Carlton K., 1942-1944 (Folder 88)
  - Mattei, A. C., 1953 (Folder 89)
  - Matthew, Raymond, 1962 (Folder 90)
  - Mattison, Mrs. J., 1953 (Folder 91)
  - Mattison, Herbert D., 1934 (Folder 92)
  - Matzen, Blanche D., 1928 (Folder 93)
  - Maurer, W. H., 1921 (Folder 94)
  - Maurey, Reuben, 1952 (Folder 95)
  - Maverick, Maury, 1934-1947 (Folder 96)
  - Maxey, Chester C., 1924-1952 (Folder 97)
  - May, Samuel C., 1932-1933 (Folder 98)
  - May, W. R., 1937 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Mayer, Henry C., 1953 (Folder 2)
  - Mayer, Joseph, 1933 (Folder 3)
  - Mayer, P. H., 1964 (Folder 4)
  - Mayer, Paul, 1932-1934 (Folder 5)
  - Maynard, W. A., 1953 (Folder 6)
  - Mayo, Edmund C., 1945 (Folder 7)
  - Mazo, Earl, 1966 (Folder 8)
  - MacArthur, Douglas, II, 1959 (Folder 9)
  - MacAvoy, Clarissa H., 1924 (Folder 10)
  - MacBride, Burt, 1933 (Folder 11)
  - MacCormick, Austin H., 1943 (Folder 12)
  - MacCrate, John, 1932 (Folder 13)
  - MacDonald, Donald, 1946 (Folder 14)
  - MacDougall, Ernest D., 1931 (Folder 15)
  - MacFarland, Hays, 1950 (Folder 16)
  - MacGrath, H. A., 1932 (Folder 17)
  - MacGregor, Duncan, 1942 (Folder 18)
  - MacGregor, Frank, 1927 (Folder 19)
  - MacGregor, John M., 1928 (Folder 20)
  - MacIver, Robert, 1930-1932 (Folder 21)
  - MacKinney, L. C., 1934 (Folder 22)
  - MacKinnon, A. C., n.d. (Folder 23)
  - MacLean, Harold O., 1953 (Folder 24)
  - MacManus, Margarita, 1938 (Folder 25)
  - MacNeil, Neil, 1964 (Folder 26)
  - McAdler, Herman, 1931 (Folder 27)
  - McAdoo, William Gibbs, 1934 (Folder 28)
  - MaAfee, Helen, 1932 (Folder 29)
  - McArdler, John P., 1931 (Folder 30)
  - McArthur, Lewis A., 1946 (Folder 31)
  - McBain, Howard Lee, 1924-1932 (Folder 32)
  - McBride, Lucia, 1928-1931 (Folder 33)
  - McBride, Malcolm L., 1923-1926 (Folder 34)
  - McBride, William M., 1951 (Folder 35)
  - McCabe, Gibson, 1949-1958 (Folder 36)
  - McCahill, Charles P., 1951-1954 (Folder 37)
  - McCall, Charles C., 1927 (Folder 38)
  - McCall, Chester H., 1936 (Folder 39)
  - McCall, W. S., 1950 (Folder 40)
  - McCarran, Margaret P., 1955 (Folder 41)
  - McCarran, Pat, 1951 (Folder 42)
  - McCarthy, Anne G., 1933 (Folder 43)
  - McCarthy, Barbara, 1959 (Folder 44)
  - McCarthy, Lucille, 1927 (Folder 45)
  - McCarthy, M., 1942 (Folder 46)
  - McCarthy, Margaret, 1918 (Folder 47)
  - McCarty, C. Walter, 1946 (Folder 48)
  - McCarty, Ira B., 1946 (Folder 49)
  - McCarty, John T., 1965 (Folder 50)
  - McCastline, William H., 1924 (Folder 51)
  - McCleary, G. A., 1928 (Folder 52)
  - McClellan, C. N. M., 1938 (Folder 53)
  - McClintock, J. O., 1932 (Folder 54)
  - McClung, Harrison, 1943 (Folder 55)
  - McClure, R. M., 1919 (Folder 56)
  - McConnell, Raymond A., 1949 (Folder 57)
  - McCook, Philip J., 1933 (Folder 58)
  - McCormack, J. S., 1935 (Folder 59)
  - McCormack, John W., 1935 (Folder 60)
  - McCormick, Anne O'Hare, 1933 (Folder 61)
  - McCormick, Charles T., 1929 (Folder 62)
  - McCormick, Fowler, 1949 (Folder 63)
  - McCormick, Mrs. Stanley, 1952 (Folder 64)
  - McCoy, Frank J., 1939 (Folder 65)
  - McCoy, Raymond, 1934 (Folder 66)
  - McCoy, Reagan, n.d. (Folder 67)
  - McCraw, William, 1927 (Folder 68)
  - McCrea, Roswell C., 1945 (Folder 69)
  - McCurdy, Henry B., 1931 (Folder 70)
  - McDarment, Corley, 1939 (Folder 71)
  - McDavid, Riley, 1954 (Folder 72)
  - McDermitt, Arthur V., 1942 (Folder 73)
  - McDermott, John Francis, 1932 (Folder 74)
  - McDonald, James G., 1932 (Folder 75)
  - McDonald, John Oliver, 1932 (Folder 76)
  - McDonald, Stewart, 1936-1937 (Folder 77)
  - McDonald, W. Stewart, 1937 (Folder 78)
  - McDougal, Robert, 1942-1947 (Folder 79)
  - McEntegart, Bryan J., 1930 (Folder 80)
  - McEntegart, Catherine J., 1926-1928 (Folder 81)
  - McEntegart, Thomas C., 1928 (Folder 82)
  - McGaher, R. E., 1932 (Folder 83)
  - McGibeny, Ruth J., 1952 (Folder 84)
  - McGoldrick, John, 1930-1949 (Folder 85)
  - McGoldrick, Joseph, 1930-1932 (Folder 86)
  - McGrath, John J., 1935 (Folder 87)
  - McGraw, Harrison, 1928 (Folder 88)
  - McGraw, James, Jr., 1939 (Folder 89)
  - McGuire, O. R., 1943 (Folder 90)
  - McIntire, Allyn B., 1955-1960 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - McIntire, James B., 1952 (Folder 2)
  - McIntosh, Millicent C., 1954 (Folder 3)
  - McIntyre, Marvin H., 1932 (Folder 4)
  - McKay, D. R., 1961 (Folder 5)
  - McKay, Douglas, 1951-1956 (Folder 6)
  - McKay, Frank J., 1938 (Folder 7)
  - McKee, J. L., 1934 (Folder 8)
  - McKee, Joseph, 1933 (Folder 9)
  - McKeehan, H. H., 1930-1934 (Folder 10)
  - McKelding, Theodore R., 1944 (Folder 11)
  - McKelvey, Mrs. W. G., 1966 (Folder 12)
  - McKelvie, Sam R., 1951 (Folder 13)
  - McKellar, Kenneth, 1933 (Folder 14)
  - McK. Gibson, Eleanor, 1931 (Folder 15)
  - McKinlay, A. P., 1934 (Folder 16)
  - McKinley, K., 1918 (Folder 17)
  - McKinney, Guy D., 1934 (Folder 18)
  - McKinney, W. P., 1932 (Folder 19)
  - McKinnie, Adele, 1919-1922 (Folder 20)
  - McKinnon, Harold R., 1954 (Folder 21)
  - McKnight, Felix R., 1961 (Folder 22)
  - McLain, Catherine, 1931 (Folder 23)
  - McLane, James W., 1917 (Folder 24)
  - McLaughlin, Bernard A., 1942-1943 (Folder 25)
  - McLaughlin, Frank Y., 1938 (Folder 26)
  - McLean, John L., 1938 (Folder 27)
  - McLemore, C. K., 1932 (Folder 28)
  - McMahon, Arthur, 1927 (Folder 29)
  - McMayer, Paul, 1932 (Folder 30)
  - McMillan, J. V., 1917 (Folder 31)
  - McMillan, R. L., 1932 (Folder 32)
  - McMillan, John M., 1938 (Folder 33)
  - McMoran, W. G., 1934 (Folder 34)
  - McMullen, Clements, 1943 (Folder 35)
  - McMyler, H. T., 1920 (Folder 36)
  - McNair, A. F., 1951 (Folder 37)
  - McNeil, Stephen, 1923-1925 (Folder 38-39)
  - McNitt, V. V., 1933 (Folder 40)
  - McTarnahan, E. F., 1932 (Folder 41)
  - Mead, George D., 1949 (Folder 42)
  - Mead, Lawrence J., 1925 (Folder 43)
  - Mead, S. C., 1926-1929 (Folder 44)
  - Mead, W. S., 1948 (Folder 45)
  - Meade, Randolph, 1933 (Folder 46)
  - Meckstroth, J. A., 1947 (Folder 47)
  - Medalie, Richard J., 1966 (Folder 48)
  - Medina, Harold, 1928-1951 (Folder 49)
  - Meehan, L. V., 1931 (Folder 50)
  - Meers, T., 1933 (Folder 51)
  - Megan, Charles P., 1928 (Folder 52)
  - Meier, Mrs. George P., 1935 (Folder 53)
  - Melekov, Leon, 1932 (Folder 54)
  - Mellor, W. Bancroft, 1939 (Folder 55)
  - Meloney, Mrs. William B., 1933 (Folder 56)
  - Mencken, H. L., 1936-1938 (Folder 57)
  - Mendoza, Salvador, 1931 (Folder 58)
  - Menefee, F. N., 1959 (Folder 59)
  - Menjou, Adolphe, 1952 (Folder 60)
  - Menson, F. G., 1941 (Folder 61)
  - Meredith, L. Douglas, 1958 (Folder 62)
  - Meredith, Robert J., 1947 (Folder 63)
  - Merkel, William R., 1962 (Folder 64)
  - Merrell, O. W., 1933 (Folder 65)
  - Merriam, Charles E., 1922-1928 (Folder 66)
  - Merriam, Frank F., 1934 (Folder 67)
  - Merriam, Robert E., 1939-1956 (Folder 68)
  - Merson, Frankie G., 1931 (Folder 69)
  - Merson, Mrs. Frank G., 1924 (Folder 70)
  - Meryweather, Thomas, 1930 (Folder 71)
  - Messerli, H. C., 1932 (Folder 72)
  - Messersmith, George S., 1937 (Folder 73)
  - Mesta, Perle, 1954 (Folder 74)
  - Metzenbaum, James, 1932-1933 (Folder 75)
  - Meyer, Anna E. H., 1927-1928 (Folder 76)
  - Meyer, Annie Nathan, 1936 (Folder 77)
  - Meyer, Eugene, Jr., 1921-1932 (Folder 78)
  - Meyer, Mrs. Eugene, 1926-1936 (Folder 79)
  - Meyer, Frank, 1962-1963 (Folder 80)
  - Meyer, Gustave, 1934 (Folder 81)
  - Meyers, F. W., 1934 (Folder 82)
  - Meyne, Gerhardt, 1931-1933 (Folder 83)
  - Michael, Charles R., 1933 (Folder 84)
  - Michael, Jerome, 1929-1931 (Folder 85)
  - Michel, W. C., 1936 (Folder 86)
  - Michelon, L. C., 1959 (Folder 87)
  - Michelson, Charles, 1944 (Folder 88)
  - Michelson, Esther, 1933 (Folder 89)
  - Mickelwait, Lowell P., 1962 (Folder 90)
  - Mickle, George W., 1951 (Folder 91)
  - Middleton, George, 1953 (Folder 92)
  - Midonik, Abraham, 1936 (Folder 93)
  - Mikell, William E., 1931 (Folder 94)
  - Mikol, Vera, 1936 (Folder 95)
  - Milam, Carl H., 1927 (Folder 96)
  - Miles, H. E., 1932 (Folder 97)
  - Miles, John R., 1965 (Folder 98)
  - Miles, R. E., 1928 (Folder 99)
  - Millar, Melville B., 1966 (Folder 100)
  - Millard, Walter J., 1924 (Folder 101)
  - Mille, Anna G. de, 1932 (Folder 102)
  - Miller, A. L., 1954 (Folder 103)
  - Miller, C. R., 1934 (Folder 104)
  - Miller, Carroll, 1932 (Folder 105)
  - Miller, Cloyd, 1932-1934 (Folder 106)
  - Miller, Dayton C., 1924 (Folder 107)
  - Miller, Ernest P., 1963 (Folder 108)
  - Miller, Gene H., 1954 (Folder 109)
  - Miller, Howard A., 1954 (Folder 110)
  - Miller, Howard S., 1954 (Folder 111)
  - Miller, Irving, 1956 (Folder 112)
  - Miller, J. S., 1940 (Folder 113)
  - Miller, James A., 1933-1935 (Folder 114)
  - Miller, Justin, 1927-1934 (Folder 115)
  - Miller, Kenneth, 1956 (Folder 116)
  - Miller, Lucy K., 1926-1927 (Folder 117)
  - Miller, Margaret Ackerman, 1931 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Miller, Roy, 1939 (Folder 2)
  - Miller, S. Lawrence, 1933 (Folder 3)
  - Miller, Spencer, Jr., 1936 (Folder 4)
  - Miller, William, 1934 (Folder 5)
  - Miller, William E., 1961-1962 (Folder 6)
  - Millholland, Ray A., 1936-1945 (Folder 7)
  - Milligan, Maurice M., 1948 (Folder 8)
  - Milliken, Carl E., 1929 (Folder 9)
  - Mills, A. K., 1936 (Folder 10)
  - Mills, Dudley H., 1932 (Folder 11)
  - Mills, Frederick C., 1936 (Folder 12)
  - Mills, Ogden L., 1945 (Folder 13)
  - Mills, Robert, 1953 (Folder 14)
  - Mills, Lucille B., 1933 (Folder 15)
  - Mims, G. L., 1956 (Folder 16)
  - Minneapolis Tribune, 1919 (Folder 17)
  - Minnesota, University of, 1919 (Folder 18)
  - Minot, George E., 1953 (Folder 19)
  - Minshall, William E., 1966 (Folder 20)
  - Minton, Melville, 1928-1953 (Folder 21)
  - Missouri Association for Criminal Justice, 1926-1927 (Folder 22)
  - Mitchell, Eugene, 1912 (Folder 23)
  - Mitchell, L., 1933 (Folder 24)
  - Mitchell, Joseph, 1930 (Folder 25)
  - Mitchell, Karl M., 1934 (Folder 26)
  - Mitchell, Paul H., 1931-1934 (Folder 27)
  - Mitchell, S. C., 1915 (Folder 28)
  - Mitchell, Walter, Jr., 1953-1956 (Folder 29)
  - Mitchell, Wesley, 1927 (Folder 30)
  - Mitros, John D., 1952 (Folder 31)
  - Mlinar, W. M., 1941 (Folder 32)
  - Moe, Henry Allen, 1931-1936 (Folder 33)
  - Moffet, Georgia, 1933 (Folder 34)
  - Mohler, Paul G., 1939 (Folder 35)
  - Mohr, Howard K., 1948-1963 (Folder 36)
  - Moley, Mrs. Arthur, 1934 (Folder 37)
  - Moley, Eva, 1927-1963 (Folder 38)
  - Moley, Frances, 1927 (Folder 39)
  - Moley, James, 1927-1934 (Folder 40)
  - Moley, Jean-Claude, 1948 (Folder 41)
  - Moley, Malcolm, 1936-1942 (Folder 42)
  - Moley, Nell, 1930-1940 (Folder 43)
  - Moley, Raymond, Jr., 1938-1963 (Folder 44)
  - Monaghan, Mary, 1931 (Folder 45)
  - Monahan, Jim, 1964 (Folder 46)
  - Monroney, A. S. Mike, 1951-1954 (Folder 47)
  - Montague, Gilbert H., 1933 (Folder 48)
  - Montgomery, J. H., 1933 (Folder 49)
  - Moody, G. L., 1934 (Folder 50)
  - Moody, Joseph E., 1958 (Folder 51)
  - Moolton, Lenore, 1928 (Folder 52)
  - Mooney, A. Hulse, 1950 (Folder 53)
  - Mooney, Edwin A., n.d. (Folder 54)
  - Moore, A. Harry, 1932 (Folder 55)
  - Moore, Alvin Edward, 1934 (Folder 56)
  - Moore, Douglas, 1935 (Folder 57)
  - Moore, Edward L., 1936 (Folder 58)
  - Moore Evell D., 1931 (Folder 59)
  - Moore, Harry A., 1936 (Folder 60)
  - Moore, Herbert, 1934 (Folder 61)
  - Moore, Jane, 1928 (Folder 62)
  - Moore, John Bassett, 1939-1943 (Folder 63)
  - Moore, H. V. D., 1933 (Folder 64)
  - Moore, Maurice E., 1934 (Folder 65)
  - Moore, Mildred, 1934 (Folder 66)
  - Moore, Roy, 1937-1948 (Folder 67)
  - Moran, Frederick A., 1929-1931 (Folder 68)
  - Monford, C. M., 1932 (Folder 69)
  - Morgan, Daniel E., 1932-1940 (Folder 70)
  - Morgan, J. P., 1934 (Folder 71)
  - Morgan, Keith, n.d. (Folder 72)
  - Morgan, W. Forbes, 1932-1936 (Folder 73)
  - Morgan, Wilbur, 1919 (Folder 74)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr., 1932-1936 (Folder 75)
  - Morley, Felix, 1941 (Folder 76)
  - Morley, H. M., 1955 (Folder 77)
  - Morphy, W. J., 1934 (Folder 78)
  - Morrel, 1918 (Folder 79)
  - Morrill, J. L., 1918-1919 (Folder 80)
  - Morris, A. J., 1934 (Folder 81)
  - Morris, Charles, 1920-1934 (Folder 82)
  - Morris, Dave, 1934 (Folder 83)
  - Morris, F. Bradford, 1957-1961 (Folder 84)
  - Morris, Paul A., 1943 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Morris, Robert, 1961 (Folder 2)
  - Morrison, deL., 1960 (Folder 3)
  - Morrison, R. W., 1937-1948 (Folder 4)
  - Morrissey, John J., 1932-1936 (Folder 5)
  - Morrissey, Thomas G., 1936 (Folder 6)
  - Morrow, Wright, 1965 (Folder 7)
  - Morse, Sidney, 1928 (Folder 8)
  - Morse, Wayne L., 1934-1945 (Folder 9-10)
  - Morton, F. W., 1932 (Folder 11)
  - Morton, Hugh, 1948-1963 (Folder 12)
  - Morton, Kathleen, 1921 (Folder 13)
  - Morton, Stanley F., 1938 (Folder 14)
  - Morton, Sterling, 1938-1960 (Folder 15)
  - Morton, Thruston, 1966 (Folder 16)
  - Mosberger, Frank R., 1934 (Folder 17)
  - Moscow, Alan Jay, 1960 (Folder 18)
  - Mosely, P. E., 1951 (Folder 19)